我很期待
Looking forward to it.
好的  到时候见  伙计
Okay, see you then, buddy.
混蛋
<i>Clump nugget!</i>
-谁是混蛋  -迈克·戈根
-Who's a clump nugget? -Mike Gogan.
我知道了  肯定又要和戈根一家子去打保龄球了
Uh-oh, must be time for bowling with the Gogans.
你是说的兵败戈根那一家子吗
Don't you mean losing to the gogans?
嘿  别这样  请大家抱着积极乐观的心态
Hey, come on, let's have a positive attitude.
我是说  我承认咱们已经连败五年了
I mean, sure we've lost to them five years in a row,
也承认比分差距从未到过五十瓶之内
And sure we've never come within 50 pins.
也承认  老爸的这一段激励演讲属历史最差
Sure. Dad gives the worst pep talks in history.
嘿  赢家是不会这么说话的
Hey, that's not the way winners talk.
老妈  如果我知道赢家如何说话
Mom, if I knew how winners talked
那我应该叫泰迪·戈根
my name would be Teddy Gogan.
好了  不知道我和你们这帮熊孩子说过没有
Well now, I don't know if I ever told you kids this,
我曾经是丹佛西南部
But I was the star of the southwest Denver.
女子保龄球队的一员猛将
Women's bowling team.
真的吗
You were?
噢  天啊  真想听听这段历史
Oh, gee, I'd love to hear about that.
感觉你好像在学校的每个俱乐部  体育队都混过
Seems like you were on every club and team at that school.
那你哪有时间上课啊
How did you have time for classes?
我不确定那所学校有课吗
I'm not even sure that school had classes.
对于我来说  更像是个活动中心
To me, it was more of an activity center.
老爸  不好意思
Dad, I'm sorry to say this,
我有点忙  不能参加今年的保龄球比赛了
But I think I'm too busy for bowling this year.
太遗憾了
Oh, man.
我觉着盖比可以接替我
I was thinking Gabe could replace me.
好吧  反正也就是走走过场
Okay, I guess we'll just muddle through,
不过我相信  你会怀念这一切的
But believe me. You're gonna be missed.
理解万岁  谢谢了  同志们
Thanks for understanding. Thanks, guys.
万岁  我们终于有机会赢了
Yes! We finally have a chance to win!
耶
<i>Yeah!</i>
你们高举双臂干嘛
Why are your arms in the air?
我们在
We're...
伸展
Stretching.
为什么要伸展
Why are you stretching?
因为我们为你今年不能参赛而欢呼
Because we're happy you're not bowling this year.
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第二十四集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E24  Alley Oops
-准备好了吗  艾薇  -准备好了
-You ready, Ivy? -Ready.
下面由泰迪·邓肯演唱国歌
This is Teddy Duncan performing the national anthem
啊  在晨曦初现时  你可看见
Oh, say can you see, by the dawn's early light...
是什么让我们如此骄傲  在黎明的最后一道曙光中欢呼
What so proudly we hail'd at the twilight's last gleaming
是谁的旗帜
Whose broad stripes and bright st... .
以上是玛丽露·温兹
And that was Mary Lou wentz.
抱歉了  泰迪  我太爱这首歌了
I'm sorry, Teddy. I just love that song.
总是感动着我
It always moves me.
这首歌能让你动动  离开这间屋子吗
Can it move you right out of the room?
你为什么要录下这首歌
Why are you recording it?
为了歌唱比赛  胜者可以得到一辆车
It's for this contest the winner gets a car.
也可以获得在丹佛掘金队比赛时
And the winner also gets to sing the national anthem.
演唱国歌的机会
At a Denver nuggets game.
然后可以给辆车
And then win a car.
好了  祝你好运
Well, good luck.
我真的很爱那首歌
I sure do love that song.
是啊  不如这样  温兹夫人
Yeah, you know, Mrs. Wentz,
我建议你去参加比赛
I'd suggest that you enter the contest,
而我只想弄辆车
But I wanna win a car.
小泰  我妈对这个不感兴趣
T, my mom's not interested.
谁说我不感兴趣
Who said I'm not interested?
知道吗  在我年轻的时候
You know, when I was younger,
我的梦想就是成为一名专业歌手
It was my dream to become a professional singer.
是吗  为什么梦想破灭了
Really? What happened?
噢  结了婚  有了艾薇
Oh, I got married, then we had Ivy.
你怪我吗  难道是我粉碎了你的梦想吗
So you're blaming me? I killed your dreams?
当然不是  宝贝
Of course not, sweetie.
是你和你爸
It was you and your father.
如果咱俩都参赛  那么赢下比赛就会有双重保障
If we both entered, we'd have two chances to win.
我很乐意参加比赛  泰迪
I would love to enter the contest, Teddy,
但是我不需要车
But I don't need another car.
没错  如果我赢了  车归我
Exactly. If I win, I get the car.
如果你赢了  车还归我
If you win, I get the car.
-我也需要车  -没你事
-I could use a car. -Stay out of this.
嘿  老妈  你干嘛呢
Hey, mom, whatcha doing?
你猜猜是谁刚申请了一个人人账号
Well, guess who just joined her very first social network?
没错  我申请了人人账号
That's right. I'm on buddy page.
看来人人网玩不下去了
So buddy page is officially not cool anymore.
-什么  -没事
-What? -Nothing.
如果你想给我发条信息  或者聊天什么的
So if you ever wanna send me a message, ims, whatevs,
尽管来吗
Just hit me up.
噢  快看看还有谁
Ooh, look who else is on here...
是奶奶
Grandma!
好了  下定决心删账号了
Yep, definitely gotta delete my account.
“你可能认识的好友  PJ·邓肯”
"buddy suggestion... P.J. Duncan."
困惑了  我应该加PJ为好友吗
I don't know. Should I be buddies with P.J.?
他求之不得
He would love that.
没错  加完好友后
Yeah, and after we're buddies
我可以在他的主页发一张他小时候的照片
I could post one of his baby pictures on his page.
干嘛发一张  多多益善啊
Why post one when you can post them all?
太好了
That is a cute one.
好了  “发送PJ·邓肯好友请求”
Okay, "send P.J. Duncan a buddy request."
发送吧  查莉
Let's do it, Charlie.
好了  按那个键  就是那个
Okay, hit that button right there.
“发送”  哈哈  干得好  查莉  了不起
"sent." ha ha! Good job, Charlie. You did it.
嘿  新的好友请求
Hey. New buddy request.
来自
From...
老妈
Mom.
果断拒绝
No thank you.
你绝对想不到
You're never gonna believe this.
-什么啊  -耶  呜
-What? -Yay! Whoo!
我赢得比赛了
I won the contest!
你想说的是这句吗
Is that what you were gonna say?
不是  我要说的是  车到手了
No. I was gonna say I won a car!
呜  我要琢磨下穿什么衣服
Whoo! I've got to figure out what to wear!
生活多美好啊
Isn't it great?
是啊  目前来说
Sure, for now.
什么叫“目前来说”
"for now"? What's that supposed to mean?
小泰  你不了解我妈  事情总会出岔子
T, you don't know my mom. Something always goes wrong.
我爸和我称之为“闪光点”
My dad and I call it "the blip."
-闪光点  -是的
-The blip? -Yeah,
在玛丽露·温兹的身上  总会有闪光点
With Mary Lou wentz, there's always a blip.
我想到了
I've got it!
我穿一条美国国旗的裙子
I'll wear an American flag dress.
和一顶红白蓝三色的帽子
And a red, white and blue hat.
上面还有小亮片
With sparklers on top.
那就是闪光点吗
So is that the blip?
不是  那只是疯癫而已
No, that's just crazy.
好了  练习时间  来看看你的水平
All right, practice time. Let's see what you got.
-噢  好耶  -耶
-Oh, yes! -Yeah!
耶
Yeah!
啊  好极了  迈克·戈根来了
Ah, great. Here comes Mike gogan.
我先去游乐场了
And I'll be in the arcade.
-鲍伯  -嘿  迈克
-Bob! -Hey, Mike!
能够击败你真高兴
Always a pleasure beating you.
我是说  见到你
I mean, meeting you.
骗谁呢  我说的就是击败你
No, I mean beating you.
好了  迈克  如果你这么肯定可以击败我们
Well, Mike, if you're so sure you're gonna beat us,
不如来点刺激的
What say we make this interesting?
赌五十块钱
Say 50 bucks.
-不如直接一百吧  -那就五百
-Let's make it $100. -Let's make it $500.
-一千  -还是五十吧
-Let's make it $1,000. -Let's go back to $50.
成交
Deal.
盖比  我们走吧
Gabe, let's go.
马上  等我把那个神秘宝箱弄上来
In a minute. Gotta get the mystery box.
-里面有什么  -我再重复一遍
-What's in it? -Let me repeat the name.
神秘宝箱
Mystery box.
也许会是什么垃圾东西  比如口哨
You know it's probably something stupid like a whistle.
口哨
A whistle?
老爸  我认识的一个孩子  他又认识另外一个孩子
Dad, I know a kid from school that knows a kid.
另外的那个孩子的表亲赢了一个神秘宝箱
Whose cousin won a mystery box.
你知道里面是什么吗  一个MP3
And do you wanna know what was in it? An mp3 player.
是吗  我知道有个孩子  他的老爸不关心这个
Yeah? Well, I know a kid who has a dad who doesn't care.
快走吧
Let's go.
-嘿  老妈  -嘿  PJ  知道吗
-Hey, mom. -Hey, P. J., you know what?
你是不是在人人网上点错了
You must have hit the wrong key on your buddy page.
因为你拒绝了我的好友请求
Because you accidentally declined my buddy request.
没有  我故意的
No, I meant to do that.
什么
What?
你不想加我为好友  为啥
You don't wanna be my buddy? Why not?
老妈  我没有别的意思  只是感觉有点丢人
Mom, I really love you, but it's kind of lame.
听着  人人网就是为了朋友间的沟通
See, buddy page is for interacting with my friends.
而美女从不与我正面交谈
And cute girls who would never otherwise talk to me.
好了  难道和一个给你生命的女人成为好友很丢人吗
Okay, it's lame to be buddies with the woman who gave birth to you?
你终于明白了
Now you're getting it.
但是  PJ  如果我们互加好友了
But, P.J., if we're buddies,
那我们就可以往对方的主页上发一些有趣的东西了
We can post fun stuff on each other's page.
这样我也可以了解你的生活动态了
And then I can find out about what's going on in your life.
你很好的解释了为什么我不加你为好友  谢了
You are so good at explaining why this is a bad idea. Thank you.
-嘿  查莉  -什么事
-Hey, Charlie? -Yeah?
如果你有人人账号  你愿意加我为好友吗
If you were on buddy page, you'd be my buddy, wouldn't you?
不  妈妈
No, mama.
我来了
Here I come!
温兹夫人  衣服真不赖啊
Mrs. Wentz, that is quite an outfit.
等着看我的帽子吧  好戏还在后面
Wait till you see the hat. The batteries are still charging.
看看我的脸  还可以吗
How's my face? Do I look okay?
是啊  美极了  很期待看见你登上超大显示屏
Yeah, you look great. I can't wait to see you on the jumbotron.
超大什么
Jumbo-what?
舞台上的大屏幕
The giant screen at the arena.
可以让两万名粉丝看见你啊
How else are 20,000 fans gonna be able to see you?
两万人
20,000?
都盯着我
All looking at me?
-没事吧  老妈  -我还没仔细想过这件事
-Are you okay, mom? -I did not think this through.
怎么把皮包放下了
Why are you putting down your purse?
因为这里没有超大显示屏
Because I'm staying here where there is no jumbotron.
-你不去了吗  -我不去了
-You're not going? -No, I am not.
不要啊  有点紧张很正常
No, okay, it's totally normal to be a little bit nervous.
所以我们只管把车开到剧场
So what we're gonna do is we're gonna drive to the arena.
你唱首歌
You're gonna sing the song.
我拿到车  然后皆大欢喜
I'm gonna win a car. Everyone's gonna be happy.
呜  不要啊
Whoa! No.
-听起来像是门锁  是吧  -猜对了
-That was the sound of a lock, wasn't it? -Yes, it was.
-她不会出来了  是吧  -猜对了
-She is not coming out, is she? -No, she's not.
-闪光点  -闪光点
-Blip? -Blip.
温兹夫人  可以出来了吗
Mrs. Wentz, you wanna come out now?
不可以  谢谢
<i>No, thank you.</i>
如果你不出来  你的梦想也不会实现了
If you don't come out, your dream won't come true.
你想弄辆车的梦想吗
The dream where you get a car?
是啊  是啊  算是一个
Yeah, yeah, that's the one.
艾薇  快说点什么
Ivy, say something.
这事怪不了我和我爸了吧
Can't blame this one on me and dad, can you?
好吧  温兹夫人
Okay, Mrs. Wentz,
你曾承诺
You made a commitment.
要上台演唱国歌
To show up and sing the national anthem.
现在你拒绝
Now you are refusing.
履行承诺
To honor that commitment.
我们的祖国  美利坚合众国
To our nation, the United States of America.
难道这就是你想要的嘛
Now is that what you wanna do?
让整个国家都失望
Let down the entire country?
没错
Okay.
嘿  老妈  怎么了
Hey, mom, how you doing?
说实话  有些郁闷
To be honest, I'm kind of upset.
好了 好了  能递给我遥控器吗
Great great. Wanna hand me that remote?
PJ拒绝加我为人人好友
P.J. Rejected me as a buddy on buddy page.
我怀疑他在隐藏着什么
Makes me think he's hiding something.
他是青少年  当然要隐藏些事情
He's a teenager. Of course he's hiding something.
不像我们这帮小屁孩  没有任何隐私
Not like us preteens. We're an open book.
我希望有办法可以看看他的人人主页
I wish there was some way I could view his buddy page.
有办法  我可以加你为好友
There is. I could confirm you as a buddy.
鉴于我加了PJ为好友
And since I'm P.J.'s buddy,
你就可以神不知鬼不觉的游览他的主页了
You'd be able to look at his page and he'll never know.
你愿意帮我
You would do that for me?
小意思  我删点东西  加你为好友
Sure, I'll just delete some things, confirm you,
然后就可以了
And you're all set.
能有一个像你这样
It is so nice having a child.
愿意帮助我监视其他孩子的孩子真好
Who will help me spy on my other children.
功劳不全在我
I can't take all the credit.
我遗传了某人的邪恶基因
I had to get my evil genes from someone.
玛丽露·温兹  我不再浪费时间了
Mary Lou wentz, I am done fooling around.
现在给我打开房门
Now I want you to unlock that door.
然后给我钻进车里
And get your butt in the car now!
泰迪  太搞笑了  再来遍
<i>Teddy, that's funny.</i> <i>Do it again.</i>
的确不错
It was pretty good.
和你说吧  我放弃了
You know what? I give up.
真是抱歉  泰迪  我就是无法在那么多人面前唱歌
<i>I'm sorry, Teddy.</i> <i>I just can't sing in front</i> <i>of all those people.</i>
等等  如果你不用
Wait, what if you didn't have to sing.
-在人们面前唱歌呢  -接着说
-In front of all those people? <i>-I'm listening.</i>
好了  我有主意了  但是我们要马上走了
Okay, I have an idea, but we really do have to go,
可以在车里解释给你听吗  能相信我吗
So can I explain it to you in the car? Will you trust me?
-好吧  泰迪  我相信你  -好的
-Okay, I trust you, Teddy. -Okay.
泰迪得到信任  泰迪得到车
Teddy gets the trust. Teddy gets the car.
-艾薇  去拿我的皮包  -艾薇得到皮包
-Ivy, get my purse. -Ivy gets the purse.
哇  耶  好球  亲爱的
Whoa, yeah! Good roll, honey.
接招吧  邓肯
Take that, Duncan.
-该你了  亲爱的  -好的
-You're up, honey. -Okay.
难道每次都要这样吗
Does she have to do this every time?
别说了  不然她还要从头再来一遍
Don't talk or she will start over.
拜托了  宝贝
Come on, precious.
老娘我现在需要你发威  大宝贝
Mama needs you now, baby girl.
-耶  -耶
-Yeah! -Yeah!
-呜  -很好
-Whoo! -All right!
保持下去
Let's keep it going.
盖比  做准备  快到你了
Gabe, get ready. Your turn's coming up.
盖比呢
Where is Gabe?
盖比  过来  到你了
Gabe, come on. It's your turn.
-到我什么了  -保龄球啊
-My turn to what? -To bowl.
还没结束吗
Is that still going on?
盖比  听着  这只是个愚蠢的游戏
Gabe, look, this is just a silly game.
咱们一家子可都指望着你呢
Your family is counting on you.
谢了  老爸  在你的说话之际
Thanks, dad, since you were talking,
我又抓到了一只兔子
I grabbed a bunny.
已经十二只了  再给我一个游戏币
I got 12 of these. Gimme another token.
做梦吧你  别玩了  跟我走
No, you're cut off. Let's go.
我一定要弄到神秘宝箱
I just gotta get this mystery box.
不要  别这样  老爸
No, come on, dad!
好球
<i>Yes!</i>
-全中  -成了  成了  管他呢  过来
-You got a strike. -Yeah, yeah, whatever. Come here.
嘿  你好吗  好啊  有游戏币吗
Hey, how you doing? Good. Got any tokens?
没有
No.
拜托了  老兄  帮小弟一把
Come on, dude, help a brother out.
可我没有游戏币
I don't have any tokens.
但你有钱  对吧
You got money, right?
我可以卖给你一些有价值的情报
I wanna sell you some valuable information.
哪种有价值的情报
What kind of valuable information?
先让我看看钱
Let me see the money.
老妈在游览你的人人主页  想监视你
Mom's looking at your buddy page to spy on you.
什么  那真是
What? That's just...
老妈看我的人人主页
Mom's looking at my buddy page, huh?
那我就陪她玩下去
Bet I could have some fun with this.
不过我要先删点东西
First I better delete some stuff.
快到了  你还好吧
It's almost time to go. Are you okay?
我没事  但你确定这万无一失吗
I'm okay, but are you sure this is going to work?
绝对没问题  你是最棒的
Totally. You're gonna be awesome.
说到棒  看看我的帽子
Speaking of awesome.
看见了  不过我认为
Yeah, I think we're gonna go.
还是不要戴帽子了
Without the hat.
-好的  -好的  好的
-Yes! -Yes yes!
好了  现在盖比要做的就是击倒两个球瓶
Yes! All Gabe has gotta do is just knock down two pins.
然后我们就赢了  盖比  你闭着眼睛都能做到  对吧
We win. You can do that in your sleep, right, Gabe?
搞什么
What happened?
游戏币玩完了
I ran out of tokens.
现在胳膊又被卡住了
And now my arm's stuck.
好了  我会向旁边挪一下  你把它抬起来
Okay, I'll scoot over and you reach up in there.
然后拿到神秘宝箱
And get that box.
遇到困难了吗  邓肯
Little problem, Duncan?
嘿  大叔  你有游戏币吗
Hey, man, you got any tokens?
如果你的孩子不能参赛  邓肯家只能弃权了
If your kid can't bowl, the Duncans forfeit.
嘿  我们不会弃权的
Hey, we are not gonna forfeit.
好吧  不过离比赛结束还有十分钟
Well, we only have the lane for another 10 minutes.
我看你还能去哪再找个邓肯家的人
Where are you going to find another Duncan?
只能赌一把了
It's a long shot,
现在邓肯家只剩她了
But there's one Duncan left.
听着  查莉  现在邓肯全家都指望你了
Okay, Charlie, the whole family's counting on you.
你现在要做的就是击倒两个球瓶
All you have to do is just knock down two pins,
然后我们就可以止住连败了
And we're not gonna be losers anymore.
-好了  上场吧  -加油
-Okay, go ahead. -Go ahead.
上吧
Go ahead.
好了  好了  别管那球了
Okay, it's okay. Shake it off.
好了
All right.
这是我们的最后一球
We're down to our last ball.
意义非凡的一球
It's a very special ball.
先生们女士们
<i>Ladies and gentlemen,</i>
请起立唱国歌
<i>Please rise for the singing</i> <i>of our national anthem,</i>
演唱者是来自丹佛的家庭主妇  玛丽露·温兹
<i>Which will be performed</i> <i>tonight by Denver housewife</i> <i>mary Lou wentz!</i>
啊  在晨曦初现时  你可看见
Oh, say can you see, by the dawn's early light
是什么让我们如此骄傲  在黎明的最后一道曙光中欢呼
What so proudly we hail'd at the twilight's last gleaming
我们就笑纳了
<i>We'll take that.</i>
干得好  查莉
Good job, Charlie.
勇者  的  家园
And the... home of the... brave
耶
<i> yeah! </i>
我说这是
<i> I said the home </i>
我说这是勇者的
家园
of the brave. .
听着  查莉  妈妈我看了PJ的人人网主页
Okay, Charlie, mommy looked on P. J.'s buddy page.
发现他们在为我举办一个惊喜派对
And found out they're throwing a surprise party for me.
-为什么  妈妈  -这个嘛  据PJ说
-Why, mama? -Well, as P.J. Put it,
是为了庆祝我是世界上最好的妈妈
It's a spontaneous celebration of the world's best mom.
当我们走进去的时候  别忘了装出惊讶来
Now when we walk in, don't forget to act surprised.
嗨  大家好  我到家了
Hi, everybody, I'm home.
他们肯定在厨房呢
They must be in the kitchen.
嗨  大家  我回来了
Hi, everybody, I'm home.
地下室  绝对在地下室呢
The basement. Definitely the basement.
嗨  大家
Hi, everybody,
我到家了
I'm home.
-嘿  老妈  -在哪呢
-Hey, mom. -Where's the...
什么在哪呢
Where's the what?
我是说  你又在说些什么
I mean, what are you talking about?
我说的是你在偷看我的人人主页
I'm talking about you snooping on my buddy page.
想和我说些什么吗
Anything you wanna say to me?
我讨厌网络
I hate the Internet.
好了  查莉  玛丽露唱了国歌
Well, Charlie, Mary Lou sang the national anthem,
我赢了辆车
And I won the car.
好了  是你赢了辆车
Well, you won the car.
看来比赛的赞助商是家玩具公司
Seems the contest was sponsored <i>by a toy company.</i>
我真应该好好读下规则细节
I really gotta read the fine print.
你不仅赢了辆车
So not only did you win the car,
你还赢了保龄球比赛
You also won the bowling tournament.
我不知道为什么我还要给你拍视频日记
I don't know why I'm leaving these video diaries for you.
你应该给我拍
You should be leaving them for me.
好运  泰迪  对吧
Good luck, Teddy, huh?
开玩笑的  好运了  查莉
I'm kidding. Good luck, Charlie.
等不及要打开神秘宝箱了
I can't wait to open this mystery box.
里面可能是任何东西
There could be anything in here.
口哨
A whistle?!
我花了五百游戏币就换了一个口哨
I spent 500 tokens on a whistle?
你好  主人
Hello, master.
哇
Whoa!
神灯精灵
A genie.
嘿  看你有些眼熟
Hey, you look kind of familiar.
人们都说我长得像布拉德·皮特
People say I look like Brad pitt.
我会满足你三个愿望  给你一分钟时间  快
I'm here to grant you three wishes. You have one minute. Go!
好吧  真希望知道要些什么
Okay, I wish I knew what to ask for.
第一个
That's one.
这也算  天啊  真希望没说刚才那句话
That counted? Man, I wish I hadn't done that.
-第二个  -我晕  呃
-That's two. -Okay. Ugh!
好了  这个一定要仔细想想
Okay, really gotta be careful on this one.
嘿  这是怎么回事
Hey, wait, what's going on?
-嘘  现在没时间  没时间  -但是  PJ
-Shh! Not now, not now. -But, P.J....
我真希望你离我远点
I wish you've leave me alone.
第三个
And that's three.
至少还剩下个口哨
Still got a whistle though.